Seino!
Galgun Channel GOGO!
Today,
I would like to make a strap!
This is a strap I made the other day,
I made this for WiGO the other day,
I had a photo shooting event.
I had an event at WiGO the other day,
After the event, I went shopping at WiGO.
After the event, I went shopping at WiGO,
And at that time, I was kind of..,
What?
I thought, "Wouldn't it be cute if I made beads on the Galgal channel? I thought it would be cute.
It's my first time.
Yay. I might be making beads for the first time, too.
I've made a lot of different kinds of, uh..,
Yeah, like, you know, little beads like this,
Big ones,
Big ribbons, stars..,
Stars, letters...
If we are going to make something, let's make it pretty.
Yes, absolutely.
Okay, let's get started. Let's start with the shape, shall we? Shape? I don't mean shape. You mean length?
Let's put it like this. And you'll work on it as you go along? Yeah, I'll do it as I go. Okay, okay.
I don't know how to do it. It's my first time making it, and I don't have any sense of style, so I'll tell you.
And this is the length, the length. Length. That's right. So, how long do you want it to be? How long do you want it?
But, you know, like this, right? Like this.
Maybe even a little longer.
It depends on where you put it.
Well, it does.
Where do you want it?
What? But isn't the phone the best place to put it?
Yeah. - Yeah.
Wait, that's it?
Is it too short?
Short?
What? I mean, just enough to put your arm through, right?
Oh, that's about right.
It's like this.
What do you call it?
It's like a DIY kind of thing.
I don't know.
I don't usually do that in private.
I don't...
But I like to do it.
I'll go put it in.
I want to see what it feels like when I put it in here.
It's huge! It's big.
But it's good for a point. - Yes, it's good for an accent.
I'm not sure. Can I just put whatever I want?
I'll put my name.
I'll put my name. Shall we say her name?
Shall we say her name?
Yes, yes, yes. You know what?
Hey, Yokasan? Hey, Yoka? Hey!
Hey! Why don't you stop?
Hey, hey, hey!
There it is.
a k a
a m n
a
One at a time
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
It's the kind of thing that would make you feel good about yourself.
I'd be all over you if it wasn't for you.
You know what?
Do you think it's cuter to talk to M?
I think you're cute.
I'm going to talk to her.
I'm going to scatter them.
It's like he came out of nowhere.
This year too...
Yes...
Oh no... oh no... oh no...
It's the second half of the year.
It's early.
I'm scared.
It means 2025 is waiting for us.
Oh no!
Time seems to be flying by so fast these days
I know, right?
Yeah, I'm scared!
Stop it!
It's bad... because I'm graduating from high school.
There will be no more high school students.
Girls...
Ladies... ladies... ladies...
Oooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo
Ha-ha-ha.
I don't want to be a wooma-wooma!
Because, you know, at the time of Delibe, I was in junior high school and high school.
That's right.
What do you want to do?
I only have 6 months left
Wow, what do I want to do?
I want to go away.
Away?
Oh, a road trip?
I don't know, we don't have to go on a trip anymore.
You know something? Like in Nagano?
There's a beautiful nature there.
I read about it on social media.
Like Gifu? Gifu? Gifu?
Gifu?
There are some really beautiful places there.
Yeah. - Yeah.
I want to go there.
You want to refresh yourself.
Yes, yes, yes.
Some place like that.
That's just if you want to go there, that's it.
I want to do it properly.
A car is the best way, right?
Yeah.
Maybe you should get a driver's license too.
On June 30th... the concert is over...
It's over, isn't it?
By the time this is out, thank you very much.
I hope you enjoyed it. We did a duet... you on piano, me on guitar.
Thank you. We sang a duet, and everyone loved it.
Isn't that a first? Showing Minami playing?
You know, the month we had the meeting...
We had a meeting the month of the set list.
Yes, yes, yes.
I was thinking of playing the piano.
I was thinking of playing the guitar.
But Yokachan was the one who wanted to play guitar.
But Yoka said the sound would be a little sad if I played alone.
I was going to play with Misaki.
But then I thought about the fact that Minami and I hadn't played together since the last time we played together.
And Misaki used to be like that, too.
Alone.
That's right.
That was the plan.
I was wondering what to do.
That's right.
Well, you wrote it down in your specialties, so I thought I should show it here.
So I put it in.
You did, right?
I said, "Okay.
But... at this point in time...
At this point in time?
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
We haven't done the Satsu Ebisu yet.
Yes, yes, we haven't done it yet.
I'm just saying, this is bad.
This is bad.
It's not good.
I'm not done yet.
Thank you for watching.
I didn't match it up. But Yokachan did match the guitar with Mi's piano once in the video.
On your own.
Yeah. Then I got a line saying how impressed I was.
Oh, yeah, yeah, it's pretty good?
Like, "It's really good!
It's pretty good.
And then she was like, oh, yeah, really? Like, "Oh, yeah, really?
But you don't know much about guitars.
So she's like, "Oh, yeah, I see.
I guess that's the beauty of that kind of storytelling.
It's like a sense of speed.
It's a feeling you can only get from a live performance, isn't it?
It's overwhelming.
So cute!
It's black.
I told you, it's a little floaty.
This is what it looks like now.
It's going to take a little bit of time.
I'll keep working on it.
Okay, so it's done!
Ta-da!
Wow!
It's so cute!
The beads were first prepared in the beginning...
Yes, I did.
Oh, by the way, shouldn't you do it first?
Yes.
Yes, we'll continue after that.
And then cut.
And then I kind of...
After that, I just threw it all out there.
So you made it from scratch.
Yes, I did.
So the atmosphere changed a lot.
The atmosphere changed.
I guess you could say it's a change in feeling. I feel like there are more big songs.
We put in a lot of big ones that don't have that kind of music, but we bought a lot of running beads in running colors in the preparation stage, so it's like we're both doing this.
I think the pink road in March is a little bit blue, or maybe the monster is a little bit blue, and this pink place on the jack-out is a piece of peace.
And this blue cat star.
It was fun!
It was a lot of fun.
I had a lot of fun with the staff.
Yes, we had a lot of fun with the staff making all kinds of straps.
Kuraray-Chan was making them, too.
We've been talking about wanting to work together for a long time.
We had been talking about it for a long time, and it finally came true.
I'm so happy!
Thank you very much for watching!
Thank you very much.
If you think this is cute
If you think it's cute and you want to make it, please subscribe to my channel and give me a high rating. Bye bye!
I'm wearing Bigo's outfit this time